[Fast forwarding...]
Yes, I did, and the live delivery has started,
Yes, please.
Yes, please do.
Let's do our best.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, hi, hi.
First of all, I'd like to introduce you all to the live streaming audience.
First of all, I'd like to introduce to you, or rather, I should say, I'd like to say that I'm launching, and I'm Yuno Nakamura.
We've been recording a lot of things right now, and we've decided on Yuno Nakamura's devil name!
Please hear it from her. It's "balicata".
What was that? Wasn't that unfair? That wasn't fair.
It sounds like Miyasaka.
How did you decide?
You're supposed to do it like this, with the swing.
Which do you prefer, a flat, round one or a tube?
If it's a tube, you hold it like this.
I'll put "balicata" in there for you.
This is the man who's launching this week.
What? What is it? It's so obvious!
I'll think of something like that. He says it's a good balicata.
Thank you, Jackie!
I don't need to introduce myself, but I'm a yellow-green, fresh-faced idiot.
Thank you very much.
You said your parents are watching us, right?
If they call their own son an idiot on TV...
I might say it because it's not a good name.
But I think he'd feel a little guilty inside.
But his mother said she was grateful.
I'm thankful for your mother.
So, you know, in a hair cut kind of way...
It's hard to say "idiot" to a man, isn't it?
That's true.
So, you know... if you write "KMSB" in the alphabet...
KMSB means "fresh yellow-green moron.
I see... Which do you prefer, KMSB or KYOROKU SENKAKU BAKA?
I'd rather be a fresh yellow-green idiot.
Let's be honest.
Let's be honest about how we really feel.
So, as usual, I'd like to present to you this week's episode.
You have a great chance to make your debut!
First of all, let's take a look at the cell phone.
I'm going in as is.
I'm going to do it.
I'm sorry, but can we have a moment of silence?
There's a silence at the beginning, so can you please be quiet?
Quiet, please.
Okay, so here we go again today.
I would like to welcome you all to Kanna TV.
Please give my best regards to everyone at Kanna TV.
Welcome.
Thank you very much.
So, we've heard a lot about this program, haven't we?
Yes.
Yes, I have received a lot of letters,
Yes, I have.
I would like to introduce you to some of them.
Please do not hesitate to contact us.
Please do.
By the way, since you are from this generation, you have learned to use computers at school and so on.
I learned a little bit about computers.
But do you do it yourself?
No, I don't.
Oh, so it's all this way?
Yes, I do.
I've already left it that way.
Young people do.
It's true that when they start working, they use this way and that way,
Yes, that's right.
Surprisingly, there aren't many people who have their own.
Maeda is in junior high school.
Wow.
What is it with me?
You are totally opposite.
And I'm in the opposite direction.
I see.
I'm saying good luck to you, Bali.
I'll do my best.
No, that's good.
Well, it's true that he usually speaks in a rather subdued tone,
Yes.
But there was a time when he spoke really loudly for a moment, right?
Yes, there was.
That was good, wasn't it?
It was good.
Actually, I think I have a very good voice.
Oh, really?
Maybe it was the voice actor, or something...he had that kind of voice, right?
Wow, that's great.
I was surprised.
No, it was a really good voice.
Blue! You said that, didn't you?
No, no, no, no, I didn't say that.
Baloo! Blue! I was saying.
You son of a bitch! all of a sudden. I was so surprised.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, let me end with a little bit louder for those of you who are watching the live broadcast.
Uh, yes.
Just a little bit.
For the service.
Yes, just a little bit.
Just a little bit.
That's good.
I'll see you later.
Later.
First, Machida City and Ayaka City in Tokyo.
Machida is said to be the hometown of the yellow green fresh fool.
Ah, yes. Thank you very much.
Nowadays, there are a lot of people from Machida who watch this devil.
Yes, that makes me happy.
So, thanks to the arrival of the Yellow-Green-Shiny-Baka, Machida has become a powerful city.
Machida.
That's great.
I'm so happy.
By the way, by the way, is that it?
You know, Balikata, do you know Machida?
I don't know Machida.
It's in Tokyo.
Well, could he please explain it to us?
Well, I don't know if I should say "explain".
Well, it is in Tokyo,
Well, Machida is rather close to Kanagawa, isn't it?
Yes, it is. It is also close to Kanagawa.
There is the Yodobashi Camera, and depending on the floor of the Yodobashi Camera, if you go this way, you go to Kanagawa, and if you go this way, you go to Tokyo,
If you go this way, you are in Kanagawa, and if you go this way, you are in Tokyo.
Oh, that's right.
That's the borderline.
That's right.
Exactly.
The city is right on the border between Tokyo and Kanagawa,
It has a large population.
It is a large city and a major residential area.
Yes, it is.
There are also quite a few companies.
That's right.
Garbage collection is amazing.
It's developing.
It's thriving, or rather, it's developing.
And they were making a lot of money.
Gappogappo. I don't think I said "gah-gah-gah.
Yes, it's that kind of town.
So, when you drive on the roads, Machida sticks out from Tokyo.
That's right.
So, when you drive along the road, it says that you entered Tokyo at Kanagawa.
After about 50 meters, it says that you have entered Kanagawa.
It's all very complicated.It's kind of complicated already.
It's a certain thing, isn't it? There is Machida, isn't there?
Yes, so this is Ayaka from Machida.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Master Ohba-san.
Yes.
Have you gotten used to it? Regular customer Nakajima-san.
Yes, I'm used to it.
It's your turn.
The other day, we were having a lot of fun talking about how tall you are, weren't we?
Oh.
181cm.
Yes, that's right.
A giant in the 180cm class.
That's right.
It's very Progressive, isn't it?
I drew the picture in the image of what we were talking about in the story.
So, I think this is exactly the story of the advancing Titans. This is it.
May I?
Yes.
It's huge!
Wow! It's a Colossal Titan.
A Colossal Titan.
It's Mr. Deltor.
No, really...it's 60 meters tall.
I'm probably at the top of the wall, wearing my three-dimensional function device, trying to figure out how I'm going to defeat this thing.
Wow, I'm so happy to see this.
This is amazing.
I'm going to be able to do it.
I'm going to pishoo it here.
Stab it here, and it will fly away, and when it starts to woo, I will turn around and stab it here,
And then they would pishoo me at the nape of my neck.
Rorogorogorogorogorogorogorogorogorogorogorogorogorogorogorogorogoro.
It's a spinning machine.
You looked like you were having a lot of fun earlier! He said something like, "Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
Well, well, well, well, well, indeed.
It's nice. The pictures are good.
The pictures you draw are unique, and I think you are probably already working on the balicata.
They are amazing. He has this unique touch, but I think they are similar.
I think it's amazing.
And one more thing, Mr. Blue Mars, from Nakahara-ku, Kawasaki City. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Right now, Kanagawa Prefectural Police is running a campaign to prevent young people from becoming victims of crimes related to JK business.
And Ebichu-chan is on the poster.
I see.
This is really amazing. May I?
Yes.
This is the poster that's out there right now.
Congratulations on your new enrollment. The so-called JK business is full of danger. I will never allow it. Don't get involved.
and then everyone is like this.
Oh, wow.
Oh, they're coming out, they're coming out, they're coming out.
They're here.
You're here, aren't you?
Oh, wow, they're here.
Well, you know. He is saying that these people are doing something bad.
That's right. It's like a closed dialogue, isn't it?
That's right.
It's like, "It's dangerous if you get involved with these people.
The picture is after the "don't get involved" message, right?
Yes, yes, yes. It's easy to make money. You can reply with sweet words. They won't cheat you.
I see.
Ah, Kanagawa Prefectural Police. Private Ebi City Junior High School.
Oh!
Amazing. This is a great lineup, isn't it?
It's huge.
There is the Kanagawa Prefectural Police Headquarters building right there.
Oh, yes, that's right.
It's amazing. It's cool, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It looks like a space station.
There's something on top, isn't there?
Yes, it is.
Yes, yes, yes. And then....
Let's see... the other thing is... well... let's see what it is.
Creature Imagination
Yeah, Shingeki's Indian.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you've heard of the creatures, but this time...
But we don't know much about how they are expressed in Chinese characters.
For example, the famous word "panda" is written "bear cat" and "bear cat" is written "panda".
I'm going to show you a kanji character now.
I'm going to give you a kanji character now and you'll be able to write it soon.
I was really surprised, wasn't I?
I was really surprised.
It's not that hard. It's amazing... maybe you can read it.
Let's see...
One character will appear.
What is it? Read it.
It's a box, right?
What's this?
It's an insect, but it's got money on it.
I've never seen this kanji before in my life.
I'm not familiar with it... so I'm going to ask you to imagine it.
I'll get right to it... because I'm afraid that if there's an answer to my comment...
There it is.
Thank you very much.
Now, now, now, now... this is for Polly, who is an expert shopper.
How do you read that?
I don't know how to read it
I'll leave this out.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Do you know it?
Who knows? This.
Well, there are a lot of sensible adults here.
Yes, of course.
They know a lot more than you'd think.
I've never seen this before.
Really?
What's it look like?
It's today's topsides and bugs of horror.
Thank you very much.
Just a hint, but I'm sure you've seen it before.
You think?
Maybe... maybe not, depending on where you are.
Maybe. Maybe not in some parts of the country.
But I'm pretty sure I've heard of them.
But I don't know if I've ever seen one in person... it depends on your lifestyle.
I'm starting to think it's not this one.
No, same here.
Also, this week... kmsb is on his third round...
He's already bursting with his drawing ability.
I'd like to share something with those of you who are watching the live broadcast.
I had a chance to draw his face.
It was amazing, wasn't it?
I'll never forget it.
When I die, maybe I'll go after that one last time.
It was a horrible picture, like, "What do you think of me?
I just made a mistake.
Okay, first of all...
Let's go to the baikata.
What did you think it was, by the way?
I thought it was either a centipede or a cockroach, and I drew both.
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
Wait a minute.
Mr. Balikata...
Your style is always the same, no matter what you draw.
No matter what you draw.
But I can see it.
This is a cockroach.
And this is a centipede.
Okay.
That's good.
It's cute, isn't it?
I don't know, it doesn't make me gawk.
You know, it's hard to count centipede legs.
It's a lot of work.
It's a little close, by the way.By the way, it's a little close.
A little closer.
Wait, I'm getting a little confident now.
It's no exaggeration to say that we live in the same world.
Wait, I'm starting to feel confident.
I'll take care of it.
This way, please.
This is a beetle.
You mean this round one?
That's right.
I see.
Pill Bug.
Beetle.
I see.
You say the same thing about everything.
Wow, you can say that about anything.
What the fuck is this?
Oh, my God.
I can't get enough of it.
You know, I've been thinking.
As of today.
I don't know how to say this, but...
You should paint.
It's a view I could get paid for.
I'm so happy.
The moment I see the painting.
I feel like my blood stops flowing.
It stops.
My body says, "Oh my God!
And then gradually it starts to come back.
That's how shocking the picture is.
It's indescribable.
By the way...
This feeling...
What a surprise!
It's a cricket!
Wow!
I heard they call them crickets now!
And they were so close.
They look a little like crickets.
I wouldn't be surprised if there were crickets here.
Well, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not bad.
I'm just saying, you know, the three of you, you've got to stop doing this.
It's the worst pattern for people who don't like bugs.
Well, well, well, well.
I hope you will continue to send us your creature imaginations!
And, I'm looking forward to seeing you all on the live feed.
The pictures with Barika are really, again...
I'm supposed to draw a cockroach and a centipede.
This week, we had a lot of different things painted.
I did a lot of drawings.
All the faces are the same!
It doesn't matter what they are.
I don't know how you can tell the difference between them.
That's why they're so distinctive.
Is this a cockroach?
It looks like he's skydiving.
Here come the cockroaches! Like that.
Well, well, well... That's why I'm here.
If you have any more creature imaginations, please send them to us again.
Please send them to us again!
Please do!
And so...
I think it's about time for the live delivery.
How was it?
This week is not over yet.
Well, there were a lot of noisy people.
I'm sorry, I thought it was a pub.
Including me and my guests.
It's too loud.
There were many times when I wished I didn't have to be so loud.
Even though we were so close.
Why do you have to be so loud?
How was it?
I was nervous at first.
But when I started talking with the noisy people...
I had a lot of fun.
So, according to Urata...
Maya Maya, as a junior member of the group.
"I'm looking forward to working with you.
He really followed up.
That's what I'm talking about.
Maya Maya Ma!
Oh, look at you! See?
Look at him!
He's so sweet.
He's so considerate.
Well then...
I think it's time for the live broadcast.
We're going to go now.
I'm sorry.
We're going out.
How many?
Three or nothing.
There might be two, though.
Basically, maybe one.
Oh, one.
Two bottles.
So that's all for now.
See you next week.
Thank you very much.